[{"id": 1548, "question": "*200 dead as Brazilian plane crashes in Sao Paulo Up to 200 people were dead after a passenger plane with 176 people aboard slid off the runway on landing and hit a fuel storage tank at Sao Paulo's Congonhas airport on Tuesday. Brazilian airline TAM said that 170 passengers and 6 crew were aboard the Airbus A320 flying from Porto Alegre in southern Brazil to Sao Paulo when it lost control on landing and slid off the wet runway. Brazilian news agency Folha reported up to 200 people were dead, including some victims on the ground. * _ Two people were killed Saturday in two separate plane crashes in the United States, media reports said. In Dayton, Ohio, a plane crashed on a runway of the Dayton International Airport while performing during the Vectren Dayton Air Show. The pilot, Jim LeRoy, w...\n\nQ: The proper title for News 2 would be   _  .", "options": ["Two pilots killed in plane crashes in US", "The tragedies of the air show", "Who is to blame for the plane crashes?", "Big losses can result from small things"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2589, "question": "Elizabeth Mitchell's new \"Liberty's Torch\" is the fascinating story of how the Statue of Liberty came to be. The Statue of Liberty's rough history is explored in \"Liberty's Torch\". Frederic Auguste Bartholdi is an all-but-forgotten figure in American history. He was, however, responsible for one of the most enduring symbols of the United States: the Statue of Liberty. A Frenchman from Alsace, he designed and built the Statue of Liberty which stood on Bedloe's Island in New York Harbor. How this statue came to be is the fascinating subject of Elizabeth Michell's new book \"Liberty's Torch\". The power of Mitchell's narrative is convincing . We recognize the Statue of Liberty now as a symbol of hope and opportunity for a nation of immigrants. At the time, though, people could not see that-nor ...\n\nQ: What type of writing is the passage?", "options": ["A travel guide.", "A book review", "An announcement", "An architecture report."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3025, "question": "While elephants are respected by the people of Thailand, they are also used as beasts of burdens . Today, these majestic animals are extensively used to help carry wood for the logging industry. It is therefore nice to hear that on National Elephant Day the mighty mammals are treated like a king, and served with meals fit for a king. One of the biggest celebrations took place at the Pattaya Resort in Thailand's Chonburi Province. Fifty-two elephants, some wearing beautiful clothes, arrived bright and early for the big day. Each was first blessed with holy water by a professional elephant rider and then led to the grand feast, which served an unlimited supply of their favorite treats--bananas, dragon fruits , pineapples, assorted melons, apples and the list went on and on! The elephants ate...\n\nQ: Nowadays elephants in Thailand are", "options": ["still used to help fight battles", "never used as beasts of burdens", "used to do tasks that need strength", "less respected because of the development of the society"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1238, "question": "Generational differences and the economy are shifting more responsibilities for children from their parents to grandparents, according to a new survey. More than one-third of grandparents aged 50 and older contribute financially to their grandchildren's upbringing, and 11 percent have a grandchild living with them, the poll by AARP, the group for 36 million older US citizens, showed. Forty percent of people who responded to the telephone survey, whose average age was 69, reported spending more than $500 on grandchildren over the past year beyond traditional gifts.Education costs accounted for 53 percent, daily expenses for 37 percent and medical costs for 23 percent.Sixteen percent provided daycare for grandchildren. \"They are the safety net for American families, helping to pay for practi...\n\nQ: Grandparents discuss with their grandchildren on various topics EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["races", "values", "drug use", "spirituality"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 56, "question": "A desert is a beautiful land of silence and space. The sun shines, the wind blows, and time and space seem endless. Nothing is soft. The sand and rocks are hard, and many of the plants even have hard needles instead of leaves. The size and location of the world's deserts are always changing. Over millions of years, as climates change and mountains rise, new dry and wet areas develop. But within the last 100 yeas, deserts have been growing at a frightening speed. This is partly because of natural changes, but the greatest makers are humans. Humans can make deserts, but humans can also prevent their growth. Algeria Mauritania is planting a similar wall around Nouakchott, the capital. Iran puts a thin covering of petroleum on sandy areas and plants trees. The oil keeps the water and small tre...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true?", "options": ["The greatest desert makers are humans.", "There aren't any living things in the deserts.", "Deserts have been growing quickly.", "The size of the deserts is always changing."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 897, "question": "Do you want to write your password down so that no one can see it, or do you want to send someone a secret message? Knowing how to make an invisible ink message will have you feeling like a secret agent in no time. These are instructions for making invisible ink using baking soda. Difficulty: Easy Time required: A few minutes What you need: Baking soda, Paper, Water, Light bulb, Paintbrush, Measuring cup, Purple grape juice Here's how: There are at least two methods of using baking soda as invisible ink. Mix equal amounts of water and baking soda. Use a paintbrush to write a message onto white paper, using the baking soda solution as \"ink\". Allow the ink to dry. One way to read the message is to hold the paper up to a heat source, such as a light bulb. The baking soda will cause the writin...\n\nQ: Why will the message appear in a different color1 in the second way to read the massage?", "options": ["Because there is enough grape juice.", "Because baking soda reacts with grape juice.", "Because of the use of water.", "Because of the special paper."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1399, "question": "An air of anxious uncertainty spread throughout the small Indian camp as the sun dawned that morning. Some braves gathered beside a smoking campfire. Murmuring sounds could be heard as they talked quietly. Women nervously performed their domestic tasks, preparing a small meal. Several sad, old men sat mute, their morale very low. The camp was pitched at the edge of a deep valley--so deep that one could barely see the calm water at the bottom. The Indians had been taken by surprise and were surrounded and attacked by enemy forces. They fought bravely, but they were degraded by defeat. Their homes were destroyed. Those who had survived had been pursued by the enemy. The chase had lasted for days. Persuaded by their leaders to press on, they had made a wrong turn. Their _ journey ended at the...\n\nQ: When the enemy braves saw the stone bridge they  _  .", "options": ["proposed a truce with the defeated Indians.", "hesitated for a while and continued to pursue the defeated Indians across it.", "were frozen with fear and escaped from the scene.", "stopped pursuing the defeated Indians."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2408, "question": "Wang Lu, 24, one of many students studying abroad who'll come home for work, majors in business & management studies at Edinburgh's Napier University. She had planned what to do after graduation in the UK: two years' work experience at a restaurant and a tour around Europe. But now her plans are up in the air. Following the UK Home Secretary's meeting on reform of the student immigration system, the UK government recently announced the end of the post-study work visa from April 2012. This will force tens of thousands of Chinese students to leave the UK after graduation. Sadly, the domestic job market doesn't welcome them with open arms. A report by Tigtag.com at the end of 2011 showed that over 35 percent of students admitted that they have employment problems. \"Returning students often ha...\n\nQ: From Xia Lei, we can learn that   _  .", "options": ["the domestic job market gives welcome to returnees with open arms", "employers prefer people who can work to those from top universities", "returnees are used to Western ways to deal with people and things around", "it is hard for returning students with creative minds to take work seriously"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 876, "question": "A new international study shows that six people die every minute from smoking. That is 3 million deaths around the world every year. If the present rate of smoking continues, the number of deaths each year from smoking could rise to 10 million by the year 2020. The study describes smoking is the biggest cause of deadly diseases among grown-ups in industrial countries. So far most of the smoking deaths have happened to men, especially in developing countries. A researcher at the World Health Organization says 70% of Chinese men smoke more than 15 cigarettes each day. In Latin America about 50% of the men are smokers. There also are a very large number of smokers in Russia and in Eastern Europe. And 25% of all smoking deaths worldwide are in those areas of the world. Scientists say smoking w...\n\nQ: A new international study shows   _  .", "options": ["three hundred and sixty smokers die from smoking every hour", "in 2020, 10 million smokers will die from smoking", "smoking will kill 50% of the men around the world", "because of the lack of money, men in developing countries smoke less than men in industrial countries"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1677, "question": "This is an excerpt from a speech by Steve Jobs, former CEO of Apple, delivered to graduates of Stanford University on June 12, 2005. I was lucky -- I found what I loved to do early in life. Woz and I started Apple in my parents' garage when I was 20. We worked hard, and in 10 years Apple had grown from just the two of us in a garage into a $2 billion company with over 4000 employees. We had just released our finest creation -- the Macintosh -- a year earlier, and I had just turned 30. And then I got fired. How can you get fired from a company you started? Well, as Apple grew we hired someone who I thought was very talented to run the company with me, and for the first year or so things went well. But then our visions of the future began to diverge(to be different) and eventually we had _ ....\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE about Apple?", "options": ["It rejected one of its founders when he turned 30.", "It once fell apart due to different visions of the future.", "NeXT became its parent company and made a great comeback.", "It has survived after it had a destructive blow."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 316, "question": "In today's Internet age, online games can be a change from the pressure of school and work. However, they can also cause problems and unhealthy addictions. This is most clearly seen in the example of South Korea. This country has the world's highest percentage of high-speed Internet services. It also has a high number of game players who are addicted to online games. In 2004, a young man died after playing online games almost nonstop for 86 hours. A 12-year-old boy stole $16,000 from his father to continue online games which he could not get away from. Such problems are spreading to other parts of Asia as well. In 2005, it was reported that about 80 percent of China's 13.8 million online game players were under 25. And many of these were said to be addicted. Such numbers point toward a gro...\n\nQ: According to the passage,   _  are more likely to become addicted to online games.", "options": ["people under great pressure from school and work", "people well-known in the field of computer games", "people with unsolved problems and few friends", "people who'd like to take a risk in computer games"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2961, "question": "Hunters in Mississippi broke a state record for the heaviest alligator ever killed, kicking off the hunting season with two big catches. Dustin Bockman of Wisconsin and two hunting friends caught the 727-pound 13-foot-long beast on Sunday, beating last year's record-setter by 26 pounds, according to the state's Department of Wildlife, Fisheries and Parks. \"We're going to cook it for sure.\" he told Gulf Live. \"There's plenty for me and everybody else.\" He and his team of hunters followed the huge creature for 12 hours until they could get close enough to shoot him with a crossbow. \"He would go to the bottom and sit like a piece of wood. You could do anything with him,\" Bockman said. The hunters then had to figure out how to drag the beast's dead body into their boat. It look four hours of p...\n\nQ: What can be inferred about the alligators in Mississippi?", "options": ["Their number is on the decrease.", "They arc no longer under protection.", "They usually weigh over 700 pounds.", "There arc enough of them for licensed hunters."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1455, "question": "Read the advertisements carefully.Then answer the questions that follow. INTERESTED IN CHILDCARE? Qualified person or preschool teacher needed for busy childcare center, south of the river.Full-time work guaranteed.Immediate start necessary.The candidate must be able to work as a co-operative team member.Phone 6345 2345 for an interview and fax resume to 6345 2345. WE NEED OFFICE CLEANERS! Three people are required for professional cleaning in the CBD area.Working hours from 5:00 pm on Mondays, Wednesdays & Fridays.Approximately five hours per shift.A good record is necessary.Experience preferred.Phone 6345 7843 now. WANT TO WORK AS A DENTAL NURSE? This is an exciting opportunity for a qualified dental nurse with a confident and cheerful personality to work in the School Dental Health Sche...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the most important for the childcare job?", "options": ["The ability to work well with other people.", "Childcare experience.", "The ability to start work in two weeks.", "Cooking skills."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 510, "question": "One day Mr. Brown sees a young woman in the street with children. He is very surprised because all the children are wearing the same clothes. White caps, blue coats and yellow trousers. \"Are all these children yours?\" he asks the woman. \"Yes, they are.\" she answers. \"Do you always dress them in the same clothes ?\" asks Mr. Brown. \"Yes,\" answers the mother. \"When we have four children, we dress them in the same clothes because we don't want to lose any of them. It is easy to see our children among other children because they are all wearing the same clothes. And now we have ten, we dress them like this because we don't want to take other children home by mistake. When there are other children among ours, it is easy to see them because their clothes are different....\n\nQ: How many people does Mr. Brown see in the street one day? He sees   _  in all.", "options": ["twelve", "eleven", "four", "ten children"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2896, "question": "Taylors English Language Preparation 2011 www.taylorscollege.edu.au/telp If you need additional help to gain the high level of English language necessary for academic study, Taylors English Language Preparation (TELP) is the perfect solution. Throughout your TELP studies you will be an active language learner. You will be surrounded by opportunities to communicate in English, with friends, teachers, families and local people. You will gain English language skills which you will keep for life. l English: the language of Taylors College Strong English language skills are necessary for success in your chosen Taylors program. The TELP program, delivered in 12 week terms, is specifically designed to provide language training for academic study. Our teachers are fully trained English Language Te...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the text that  _  .", "options": ["TELP courses permits students to have lessons at any time", "start date of the first term in 2012 is probably January 16th", "students who study from 20th December to 14th January have cold weather", "High School and Foundation programs at Taylors college have no entry requirements"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1212, "question": "For almost two months Dominic York, a 23-year-old hairdresser, wandered about hospitals all night, wearing a white coat and pretending he was a doctor. Yesterday he proudly claimed in court that despite his complete lack of medical experience or qualifications, he had saved several people's lives. He had even been allowed to assist a surgeon during an emergency operation on a patient who was about to die on something she had swallowed. \"I watched one of those TV dramas about a hospital and suddenly I felt like playing one of the roles myself. So I put on a white jacket and a stethoscope and walked around one of the biggest hospital in London. At first I just watched. Once you learn how doctors talk to patients, nurses and others doctors, it's easy to take people in,\" he said. One of the pa...\n\nQ: The judge's remark implied that York would be more severely punished if he    _   .", "options": ["pretended to be a psychiatrist", "tried to get away from prison", "was proud of what he had done", "studied the behaviour of the psychiatrist"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1055, "question": "Mrs. Allen's husband died ten years ago when her son and daughter were still in high school. Mr. Allen had left some money, and since Mrs. Allen had managed a bookstore before she was married, she took the money and bought a shop in town. Later she moved the shop out to the shopping center. She was a pleasant woman; she worked hard and was well-informed about books, and so the bookstore prospered and she was able to hire a friend to help her. Laura Barnes, Mrs. Allen's friend and assistant, was also a widow. She had some free time and the need for a little extra-money, and so she took the job in the bookstore. She was too clever and friendly, and the two women were well-known in the neighbourhood as \"Mrs. A\"and \"Mrs. B\"....\n\nQ: Why did Mrs. A hire Mrs. B?   _  .", "options": ["Mrs. B asked for very little pay", "She believed that Mrs. B was the very person to help her to improve management", "Mrs. B was a friend of hers", "she was also that kind of woman like her"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 408, "question": "I was brought up in the British, _ . Strong feelings aren't something you display in public. So, you can imagine that I was unprepared for the outpouring of public grief at a Chinese funeral. My editorial team leader died recently after a short illness. He was 31. The news was so unexpected that it left us all shocked and upset. A female colleague burst into tears and cried piteously at her desk. Somehow we got through the day's work. The next day was the funeral. Our big boss stepped forward to deliver a eulogy and was soon in tears. She carried on, in Chinese of course, but at the end said in English: \"There will be no more deadlines for you in heaven.\" Next came a long-term colleague who also dissolved in tears but carried on with her speech despite being almost overcome by emotion. The...\n\nQ: According to the writer, people in the West  _  .", "options": ["are not willing to be sad for the dead", "prefer to control their sadness in public", "cry their eyes out at the public funeral", "have better way to express sadness"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3473, "question": "The story goes that some time ago,a man punished his 3-year-old daughter for wasting a roll of gold wrapping paper.Money was tight and he became infuriated when the child tried to decorate a box to put under the Christmas tree.Nevertheless,the little girl brought the gift to her father the next morning and said,\"This is for you,Daddy.\" The man was embarrassed by his earlier overreaction,but his anger flared again when he found out the box was empty.He yelled at her,stating,\"Don't you know,when you give someone a present,there is supposed to be something inside?\" The little girl looked up at him with tears in her eyes and cried,\"Oh,Daddy,it's not empty at all.I blew kisses into the box.They are all for you,Daddy.\" The father was crushed.He put his arms around his little girl,and he begged f...\n\nQ: Which of the following would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The kisses in the box", "A girl and her father", "A love story", "The box under the Christmas tree"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1989, "question": "Recently, South Korean star PSY's 'Gangnam style\" video has been popular on the Internet. It has become most people's favorite music. In fact, the song has set the Guinness World Record for the most popular video in the history of the Internet. More than two million people have said \"like\" since the song was on the Internet on July 15. PSY\"s special dance moves and funny horse riding style have attracted many people. Although many people do not understand the language, the video has become the talk of the Internet. The song has come to first place in the music charts in 31 countries, including the United States, the United Kingdom, and Canada. \"I just sang for my South Korean fans. I have never expected it to be popular in other countries,\" PSY told the reporters on a concert. The song was...\n\nQ: Why did some of South Korea's politicians show PSY\"s moves?", "options": ["They wanted to tell people that they were also fond of music.", "They wanted people to support them.", "They were PSY's fans.", "They liked PSY's dancing style."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2458, "question": "After 10 seasons wearing the No.8 on his back, Kobe Bryant will become No.24 next season. The reason for the surprising decision by the Los Angeles Lakers super guard last week has become a hot topic for debate. Bryant wore No.24 when he was in early high school, but he changed to No.33 in his senior year. He switched to No.8 when he was selected by the Lakers in 1996, and has been not changed since. Bryant has refused to explain the decision until the end of the play-offs. So guessing Bryant's motive has become a popular game among NBA fans and newspaper columnists. There are all kinds of speculations . Many say that Bryant wants to leave the past behind and have a fresh start. He has often been criticized for playing to benefit himself and not the team as a whole. Others say that he may ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT a speculation about Bryant's motive to change his number?", "options": ["He wants to leave his past behind and have a fresh start.", "He wants to compare himself to Jordan.", "He wants to earn more money.", "He wants to show that he is man of great importance."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3132, "question": "I still remember my first day at school in London and I was half-excited and half-frightened. On my way to school I wondered what sort of questions the other boys would ask me and practiced all the answers: \"I am nine years old. I was born here but I haven't lived here since I was two. I was living in Farley. It's about thirty miles away. I came back to London two months ago.\" I also wondered if it was the custom for boys to fight strangers like me, but I was tall for my age. I hoped they would decide not to risk it. No one took any notice of me before school. I stood in the center of the playground, expecting someone to say \"hello\", but no one spoke to me. When a teacher called my name and told me where my classroom was, one or two boys looked at me but that was all. My teacher was called...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["boys were usually unfriendly to new students", "the writer was not greeted as he expected", "Brian praised the writer for his cleverness", "the writer was glad to be a goalkeeper"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3486, "question": "Mr. Briggs got a job with an insurance company after he left school and went around visiting people in their homes to sell them life insurance. One day, after he had been working for the company for about a year, the insurance manager sent for him and said, \"Mr. Briggs, I have been looking at your record as a salesman with our company, and there is one thing that surprises me about it. Why have you been selling insurance only to people over 95 years old, and why have you been giving them such generous conditions? You'll ruin our company if you go on like that. \" \"Oh, no, sir,\" answered Mr. Briggs at once, \"Before I started work, I looked at the figures for deaths in this country during the past ten years, and I can tell you that few people die at the age of 95. \"...\n\nQ: What was it that surprised the manager?   _", "options": ["Mr. Briggs sold life insurance only to 95 people.", "Mr. Briggs sold insurance only to people of more than 95.", "Mr. Briggs had ruined the insurance company.", "Mr. Briggs gave people generous conditions."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 856, "question": "The South Pole is a particular place on the earth.When people stand at the top of it looking around,they will find all directions face to north.No matter how they make their first step in which direction,they will always walk towards the north.That's to say,only north and south exist there,neither east nor west exists. At the top of the South Pole,any clock or watch keeps good time because all meridians join there.All kinds of local time are completely suitable there.It is even difficult to distinguish New Year's Eve from New Year's Day. The explorers and scientists from different countries always fix the time according to their own.Therefore the time by their watches was different when the people with different nationality gathered there. The Winter Solstice is an important festival at th...\n\nQ: On the Winter Solstice,  _   is the shortest in a year.", "options": ["the night", "the noon", "the morning", "the daytime"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 987, "question": "People can be addicted to different things -- e.g. alcohol, drug, certain foods, or even television. People who have such an addiction are compulsive :They have a very powerful psychological need that they feel they must satisfy. According to psychologists, many people are compulsive spenders. They feel that they must spend money. This compulsion, like most others, is impossible to explain reasonably. For compulsive spenders who buy on credit , charge accounts are even more exciting than money. In other words, compulsive spenders feel that with credit, they can do anything. Their pleasure in spending large amounts is actually greater than the pleasure that they get from the things they buy. There is even a special psychology of bargain hunting. To save money, of course, most people look fo...\n\nQ: From the text we may safely conclude that compulsive spenders or compulsive bargain hunters   _  .", "options": ["are really unreasonable", "need special treatment", "are really beyond drugs", "can never get any help to solve their problems with money"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 837, "question": "Scholarship Application Tips in 2014 for college students *Before you apply 1. Work hard to get good grades. Don't sweat about one bad grade, but always strive to do your best. 2. Get involved, and stay involved, in extracurricular activities. Sports, clubs, drama, bands and orchestras-these often count toward a student's overall scholarship application evaluation. The same goes for paid (or unpaid) work experience. 3. Begin your scholarship research early-by your sophomore or junior year of high school, if possible. Make special note of application deadlines, as they can vary from late summer to late spring. 4. Apply for as many scholarships as you are eligible for-several smaller scholarships can add up to a lot of money. *During the application process 1. Read the supplementary material...\n\nQ: When answering questions on the application form, you should  _  .", "options": ["focus on the subject you are interested in", "answer to the point", "list your advantages", "prove your abilities"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3150, "question": "Paul received an automobile from his brother as a Christmas present. On Christmas Eve when Paul came out of his office, a street boy was walking around the shiny new car, admiring it. \"Is this your car, Mister?\" he asked. Paul nodded. \"My brother gave it to me for Christmas.\" The boy was astonished. \"You mean your brother gave it to you and it didn't cost you anything? Boy, I wish....\" He hesitated. Of course Paul knew what he was going to wish for. He was going to wish he had a brother like that. But what the kid said made Paul quite surprised. \"I wish,\" the boy went on, \"that I could be a brother like that.\" Paul looked at the boy in astonishment, and then impulsively he added, \"Would you like to take a ride in my automobile?\" \"Oh, yes, I'd love that.\" After a short ride, the boy turned ...\n\nQ: Why did what the boy said surprise Paul?  _  .", "options": ["Because he didn't say what Paul had expected.", "Because he didn't say that he wanted a ride.", "Because he said something impolite.", "Because he said something improper."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1664, "question": "Many facts suggest that children are overweight and the situation is getting worse, according to the doctors. I feel there are a number of reasons for this. Some people blame the fact that we are surrounded by shops selling unhealthy, fatty foods, such as fried chicken and ice cream, at low prices. This has turned out a whole generation of grown-ups who seldom cook a meal for themselves. If there were fewer of these restaurants, then probably children would buy less take-away food. There is another argument that blames parents for allowing their children to become overweight. I agree with this, because good eating habits begin early in life, long before children start to visit fast food shops. If children are given fried chicken and chocolate rather than healthy food, or are always allowed...\n\nQ: The author thinks that children are becoming overweight because", "options": ["their parents often cook meals for them", "they are too busy to go out and play", "they can' t choose what to eat", "there are too many fast food shops around"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1356, "question": "When people get bad toothaches, they often have to eat soft, easily chewed food. When lions get bad toothaches, they eat people? That' s the conclusion of a zoologist at the Field Museum of Natural History in Chicago and a dentist who works on carnivores ., Lions don't normally prey on people. Every once in a while, however, a lion will go on a human-eating diet. The most famous such tragedy happened in 1898, when two lions killed and ate 135 railway workers in prefix = st1 /Kenya. Examining the preserved skulls of the two big cats, zoologist Bruce Patterson and dentist Ellis Neiburger found that both animals had been suffering from several dental and |aw problems. One lion had three missing teeth and a loose, unsteady lower canine that was probably useless. Canines are pointed teeth that ...\n\nQ: The original aim of the study is to look for   _  .", "options": ["ways of protecting wild animals", "ways of treating toothaches of lions", "when and where lions eat people", "reasons for some lions eating people"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2447, "question": "PEOPLE who have had a painful experience may wish they could wipe the memory from their minds. Researchers at Johns Hopkins University, US, say that this may someday be possible. A drug remains far off, but researchers have laid a foundation with their discovery that proteins can be removed from the brain's fear center to cut memories forever. Previous research had already shown that a special behavior therapy could cut painful memories. But relapse was possible because the memory hadn't necessarily disappeared. By looking at that process, Richard Huganir and Roger Clem, two researchers from Johns Hopkins University, discovered a \"window of vulnerability \" when proteins are created. The proteins help signals travel within the brain as painful memories are made. Because the proteins are uns...\n\nQ: What have researchers at Johns Hopkins University found recently?", "options": ["A new drug to erase painful memories from human brains.", "A special behavior therapy to erase painful memories.", "Removing certain proteins from the brain can wipe painful memories.", "Erasing memory damages a patient's brain functions."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2229, "question": "Thanksgiving Day was near. The first grade teacher gave her class a fun task----to draw a picture of something for which they were thankful. Most of the class would celebrate the holiday with turkey and other traditional goodies of season. These, the teacher thought, would be the subjects of her students' art. And they were. But Douglas made a different kind of picture. He drew a hand. Nothing else. Just an empty hand. Douglas was a different kind of boy. Most of the time, as other children played together, Douglas was likely to stand close by her side. Everyone could guess the pain he felt from his eyes. His picture interested other students. Whose hands could it be? One child guessed it was the hand of a farmer, because farmers raise turkeys. Another suggested a police officer, because t...\n\nQ: Douglas drew an empty hand in order to  _  .", "options": ["show thanks to his teacher", "ask for a turkey", "attract other students' attention", "make the teacher cry"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1490, "question": "It is the goal of politicians everywhere-----how to win and keep the trust of voters. Now researchers at the University of St Anurew's in Scotland say they may have the answer. They believe politicians could learn a lot from recent advances in science. A growing number of studies have shown that people do judge a book by its cover. Researchers say most of us make quick judgments about a person on the basis of how they look. Studies suggest that people are less likely to trust those with particularly masculine features, such as a square jaw, small eyes or a big nose. \" They are considered dominant and less trustworthy,\" says Ms Cornwell. \"It doesn't mean that men who look more masculine are less trustworthy-----it's just our first impression.\" Those with less masculine features-----larger e...\n\nQ: According to Ms Cornwell, we can infer that   _  .", "options": ["the science will give politicians great help", "politicians could be successful with the help of the science", "politicians won't think highly of the science", "politicians will be satisfied with the science"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2068, "question": "The Internet has become a part of our everyday life and there is nothing we can do without it.It is a means of communication as well as a good way of relieving and having fun.No matter in what place of the world,the Internet is the same for every one of us. If we hope to improve our knowledge or look for a certain piece of information, the Internet is the perfect tool for our need.If we do not have the time to shop, ordering online is the solution to our problem.The Internet is very useful to most people. There is no doubt that the Internet also has some bad points.I'm speaking about the harmful information,which may come up in the most unexpected paces.You can sometimes come across violence,presented to the public as a very normal way of expressing beliefs.An intelligent person will alway...\n\nQ: In the writer's opinion, who should help children avoid the harmful information on the Internet?", "options": ["Parents.", "Teachers.", "1he pubic.", "Some organization."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 399, "question": "The Internet has led to a huge increase in credit-card fraud. Your card information could even be for sale in an illegal web site. Web sites offering cheap goods and services should be regarded with care. On-line shoppers who enter their credit-card information may never receive the goods they thought they bought. The thieves then go shopping with your card number -- or sell the information over the Internet. Computers hackers have broken down security systems, raising questions about the safety of cardholder information. Several months ago, 25, 000 customers of CD Universe, an on-line music retailer , were not lucky. Their names, addresses and credit-card numbers were posted on a Web site after the retailer refused to pay US $157, 828 to get back the information. Credit-card firms are now...\n\nQ: How many pieces of advice does the passage give to you?", "options": ["Four.", "Three.", "Five.", "Six."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3123, "question": "As part of an effort to improve treatments for life-threatening illnesses, a team of scientists have created rabbits that glow in the dark. The efforts have produced two rabbits out of a litter of eight that went from being a normal, soft white to glowing green in the dark. The rabbits were born at the University of Istanbul as part of the cooperation between scientists from universities in Turkey and Hawaii. The rabbits glow to show that a genetic operation technique can work efficiently. \"The green is not important at all--it's just a marker to show the experiment can be done successfully,\" said University of Hawaii associate professor, Stefan Moisyadi. To produce the glowing effect, researchers injected jellyfish DNA into a mother rabbit's embryos. Then those embryos were put into the m...\n\nQ: What is Moisyadi's attitude towards such experimentation?", "options": ["Doubtful", "Supportive", "Disapproving", "Indifferent"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1230, "question": "When your pet has an emergency, first aid is not a _ for veterinary treatment. However, before you are able to get your pet to a veterinarian , knowing some basic first aid can help. Bite Wounds Approach the pet carefully to avoid getting bitten. Wear a mask for the animal and then check the wound. Clean the wound with large amounts of saline . If these are not available, then regular water may be used. Wrap large open wounds to keep them clean. Bleeding Apply firm, direct pressure over the bleeding area until the bleeding stops. Hold the pressure for at least 10 minutes. Avoid bandages that cut off circulation. _ Check to see if the animal is choking on a foreign object. If an animal is not breathing, place it on a firm surface with its left side up. Check for a heartbeat. If you hear a h...\n\nQ: What's the suitable subtitle for the blank ?", "options": ["Cutting", "Breathing Stops", "Poisoning", "Suffering Heart Problems"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1894, "question": "BERLIN(AP)--A tiger escaped its enclosure at Cologne Zoo in western Germany on Saturday and killed a female keeper before being shot dead by the zoo's director,police said. The tiger slipped through a passage between the enclosure and a neighboring storage building,where it fatally attacked the 43yearold keeper,said police spokesman Stefan Kirchner. \"It appears the gate wasn't properly shut,\" Kirchner told the Associated Press. The zoo was evacuated and a SWAT team was called in,police said.But before it arrived the zoo's director managed to kill the tiger by climbing onto the storage building and shooting it through a skylight using a rifle. Kirchner said it was unlikely that members of the public had witnessed the incident.\"This is the darkest day of my life,\" the zoo's director,Theo Pag...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be the best title of the news text?", "options": ["Tiger Escaped,Killed a Keeper in German Zoo", "Tiger Escaped in German Zoo,Shot Dead", "German Zoo Keeper Shot Escaped Tiger", "People Killed in One of the Oldest Zoos in Germany"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2165, "question": "Many people earn their living with their hands. Ed earns his living with his feet! And a very good living it is, too. Ed's story began in a very small town in Brazil. His father and mother were very poor. Seven people lived in their tiny house. Ed's father often played football. Little Ed wanted to play football too. So his father made a soft ball for him to kick. It was a sock filled with soft materials. The little boy kicked it every day. At last Ed learned to kick a real football. By the time he was 11, he played football very well. One day Ed was playing with some men. A man passing by saw how fast the boy ran. He stopped to watch. How well Ed kicked the ball! After the game, the man called Ed to him. \"My name is Mr. Dee,\" he said. \"I used to play football for a living. Will you let me...\n\nQ: When he first saw Ed playing football, Mr. Dee was attracted by  _  .", "options": ["his young age", "his running speed", "his love for football", "his playing with men"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3495, "question": "Do you know how to play a game called \"Musical Chairs\"?It is easy to play and most people enjoy it. All you need are some chairs, some people and some way of making music. You may use a piano or any other musical instrument, if someone can play it. You may use a tape recorder. You can even use a radio. Put the chairs in a row. The chairs may be put in twos, back to back. A better way is to have the chairs in one row with each chair facing in the opposite direction to the chair next to it. The game is easy. When the music starts, the players walk round the chairs. Everyone goes in the same direction, of course, they should walk in time to the music. If the music is fast they should walk quickly. If the music is slow, they should walk slowly. The person playing music cannot see the people in...\n\nQ: The chairs should be put   _  .", "options": ["with the desks", "before the winner", "all over the room", "in a line"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 849, "question": "Even if you are a good high-jumper, you can jump only about seven feet off the ground. You cannot jump any higher because the earth pulls you hard. The pull of the earth is called gravity. You can easily find out the pull of the earth. If you weigh yourself, you will know how much gravity is pulling you. Since there is gravity, water runs down hill. When you throw a ball into the air, it falls back down. Because of gravity, you do not fall off the earth as it whirls around. Then, can we get away from the earth and go far out into space? Now you can do it, because spaceships have been invented. Then spaceship will go so fast that it can escape the earth's gravity and carry you into space....\n\nQ: Gravity is strong that  _", "options": ["it can throw a ball into the air.", "it makes you jump only seven feet.", "it can let you fly away from the earth.", "it can keep everything on earth."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1498, "question": "Love Is Just a Thread Sometimes I really doubt whether there is love between my parents.Every day they are very busy trying to earn money to pay the high tuition for us.They don't act in the romantic ways that I read in books or I see on TV.\" I love you\" is too luxurious for them to say .Sending flowers to each other on Valentine's Day is even more _ .My father is easy to lose his temper, especially when he's very tired from the hard work. One day, my mother was sewing a quilt.I silently sat beside her and asked her if there was love between them.\" What?\" she replied, still doing her work.My mother stopped her work and raised her head with surprise.She didn't answer immediately.Then she bowed her head and continued sewing the quilt.I was in a great embarrassment and I didn't know what to d...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of the text?", "options": ["We should understand our parents.", "Love is inside, making life strong and warm.", "Love is really very important to anyone.", "Love should be outside, and can be seen everywhere."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 823, "question": "There are millions of used cell phones in the world today. Most of them just lay in our houses without any purpose. Every day dozens of new cell phone models appear. Today, you can find what was regarded as a fantasy yesterday in store and you will buy it tomorrow. But what to do with the old phones, which work well enough and not so old? Just get some money! Simply Sellular is buying almost all models of cell phones: LG, Motorola, Siemens, Samsung, Sanyo, Nokia and many other cell phones. Also they accept phones produced in every country, and in every condition. Simply Sellular can offer a good price for your old cell phone in cash. Their mission is giving you a simple way to get money for an old phone, as simple and profitable, as possible. Also they offer a trade-in scheme to get anothe...\n\nQ: When you want a new cell phone, you are advised to    _  .", "options": ["keep the old one in house", "throw the old one into the dustbin to protect your health", "return the old one to the producer to get some money", "sell the old one to Simply Selluar on a reasonable price"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1367, "question": "Tom appeared on the sidewalk with a bucket of whitewash and a long-handled brush. He stopped by the fence in front of the house where he lived with his aunt Polly. He looked at it, and all joy left him. The fence was long and high. He put the brush into the whitewash and moved it along the top of the fence. He repeated the operation. He felt he could not continue and sat down. He knew that his friends would arrive soon with all kinds of interesting plans for the day. They would walk past him and laugh. They would make jokes about his having to work on a beautiful summer Saturday. The thought burned him like fire. He put his hand into his pockets and took out all that he owned. Perhaps he could find some way to pay someone to do the whitewashing for him. But there was nothing of value in hi...\n\nQ: What made Ben Rogers eagerly gave up his apple and offer to brush the fence for Tom?", "options": ["His curiosity about Tom's brushing job.", "His warm heart and kindness to friends.", "Tom's threat.", "Aunt Polly's idea."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1729, "question": "When we see well, we do not think about our eyes very often. It is only when we cannot see perfectly that we realize how important our eyes are. People who are near-sighted can only see things that are very close to their eyes. Everything else seems blurry (unclear). Many people who do a lot of work, such as writing, reading and sewing become near--sighted. People who are far-sighted _ from just the opposite problem. They can see things that are far away, but they have difficulty in reading a book unless they hold it at arm's length. If they want to do much reading, they must get glasses, too. Other people do not see clearly because their eyes are not exactly the right shape. They have what is called astigmatism . This, too, can be corrected by glasses. Some people's eyes become cloudy bec...\n\nQ: People who suffer from astigmatism have  _  .", "options": ["one eye bigger than the other", "eyes that are not exactly the right shape", "a difficulty that can be corrected by an operation", "an eye difficulty that cannot be corrected by glasses"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2888, "question": "A month after Hurricane Katrina, I returned home in New Orleans. There lay my house, reduced towaist-high ruins, smelly and dirty. Before the trip, I'd had my car fixed. When the office employee of the garage was writing up the bill,she noticed my Louisiana license plate. \"You from New Orleans?\"she asked I said I was, \"No charge.\"She said, and firmly shook her head when I reached for my wallet. The next day I went for a haircut, and the same thing happened. As my wife was studying in Florida, we decided to move there and tried to find a rental house that we could afford while also paying off a mortgage (> on our mined house. We looked at many places, but none was satisfactory. We'd began to accept that we*d have to live in extremely reduced circumstances for a while, when I got a very curi...\n\nQ: What do we know about James Kemnedy?", "options": ["He was a writer of an online magazine.", "He was a poet at the University of Florida", "He offered the author a new house free of charge.", "He learned about the author's sufferings via e-mail"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2476, "question": "The United Nations says forty million people or so around the world went hungry in 2008, mainly because of higher food prices. Early estimates from the UN Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) show that 963 million people did not get enough to eat. World food prices have dropped since early 2008. Prices of major crops have decreased by more than half from their height earlier last year. But they remain high compared to earlier years. But FAO official Hafez Ghanem says lower prices have failed to end the food crisis in many poor countries. \"For millions in developing countries,\" he says, \"getting enough food every day to live an active and healthy life is a distant dream.\" The FAO says food shortage is a threat to people's health. Today, two-thirds of the world's _ people live in just a f...\n\nQ: Ghana has reached the targets of hunger reduction mainly because of   _  .", "options": ["the still high food prices", "the donation of developed countries", "the two targets of hunger reduction", "the growth in agricultural production"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 113, "question": "Any high school students lucky enough to be accepted to Harvard University can easily count themselves among the country's best and brightest. The story of David Boone's journey from sleeping on a park bench to one of Harvard's dorm rooms, certainly stands out from the crowd of his peers. David, a 17-year-old senior at a MC2 Stem, a high school in Cleveland, Ohio that focuses largely on engineering and science classes with the help of a grant from the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation, was offered a full-ride scholarship to Harvard in the fall. His family life has been complicated for the past few years after gangs and economic hardships resulted in him being separated from his family and forced to look after himself on the streets and park benches in Cleveland. Because both his grandmothe...\n\nQ: According to the passage, what is one of the reasons that made David homeless?", "options": ["His parents' divorce.", "His parents' unemployment.", "His desire to be adventurous", "His facing acts of violence."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 445, "question": "The challenge to drink to the limits of one's endurance has become a celebrated part of college life. In one of the most extensive reports on college drinking thus far, a 1997 Harvard School of Public Health study found that 43 percent of college students admitted binge drinking in the preceding two weeks (Defined as four drinks in a sitting for a woman and five of a man, a drinking binge is when one drinks enough to risk health and well - being ) Experts estimate that excessive drinking is involved in thousands of student deaths a year. And the Harvard researchers found that there has been a dramatic change in why students drink. 39 percent drank \"to get drunk\" in 1993, but 52 percent had the same objective in 1997. \"What has changed is the across - the - board acceptability of intoxicati...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that young people today_.", "options": ["cherish their dream and are willing to work hard for it.", "value spiritual satisfaction over physical satisfaction.", "are idealistic and disillusioned by the dark reality.", "seek immediate satisfaction and indulge themselves too much"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 720, "question": "Alice's mother died when she was five. Although her brothers and sisters were loving and caring, their love couldn't take the place of a mother's. In 1925 Alice became my mother and told me that her family couldn't even afford her a doll. One afternoon in December 1982, when I was getting ready for Christmas, I suddenly decided to buy two dolls, one for my five-year-old daughter, Katie, and one for my old mother. Things went smoothly when a friend told me that his dad, who played Santa Claus in my area, would be willing to make a visit on Christmas morning to our home with the gifts! Knowing that my parents would also come to my house, I began to get ready for the most memorable day of my mother's life. Christmas Day arrived and so did Santa Claus at the planned time. Katie was very excite...\n\nQ: The author wrote the message card in order to   _  .", "options": ["show her deep apology to her mother", "make it clear that Santa Claus didn't forget her", "show that Santa Claus was hard-working", "make Alice believe the gift was exactly for her"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2081, "question": "Monkeys are very similar to us in many ways. We enjoy watching them because they often act like us. In fact, scientists say monkeys and humans share a common ancestor. Monkeys make us smile, too, because they are creatures full of playful tricks. This is why many monkey expressions are about tricky people or playful acts. One of these expressions is monkeyshines, meaning tricks or foolish acts. So, when a teacher says to a group of students: \"Stop those monkeyshines right now!\", you know that the kids are playing, instead of studying. You might hear that same teacher warn a student not to monkey around with a valuable piece of equipment. You monkey around with something when you are touching or playing with something you should leave alone. Also, you can monkey around when you feel like do...\n\nQ: How many expressions about monkey are introduced in the passage?", "options": ["5.", "6.", "7.", "8."], "answer": 1}]